1. randomEmail = custom.RandomData.generateRandomEmail()
5. randomFirstName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomFirstName()
9. randomLastName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomLastName()
13. randomPhone = custom.RandomData.generateRandomPhone()
17. randomAddress = custom.RandomData.generateRandomAddress()
21. randomCode = custom.RandomData.generateRandomCode()
25. openBrowser(URL)
29. custom.BrowserHelper.setupBrowserWindow()
33. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
37. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
41. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-account"), "agungpriyadi")
45. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Password"), "Laskar123456")
49. click(findTestObject("Login/btn-sign in"))
53. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
57. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Address Management/Shipping Address/btn_My Address"), 4)
61. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Shipping Address/btn_My Address"))
65. editBtn = new com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.TestObject()
69. editBtn.addProperty("xpath", EQUALS, "(//button[contains(.,'Edit')])[1]")
73. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Shipping Address/btn_Edit"))
77. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_First Name"), 10)
81. clearText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_First Name"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
85. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_First Name"), randomFirstName)
89. clearText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_Last Name"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
93. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_Last Name"), randomLastName)